so wake up I'm the legend of Israel and
today we're reviewing the versus Bob
now the versus Bob stands about
5 12 6 you know um I'm not sure if
that's like a regular height for these
guys but uh that's what you're working
with and of course the versus Bob has
arms and legs alright so a question that
I do get about the versus Bob is
does it come separately you know it all
comes together also you're able to take
it apart okay so underneath this arm
sleeve upper torso is is an actual Bob
inside you have the ABS all that stuff
as for the mold which is
which is important to me because I
didn't want to hit something and just
have it flap around which I heard that
the Bob XL is like that so the original
Bob you know it it wasn't soft you know
it was like hard rubber Bam Bam you know
and if you don't hit it with protection
then you're you know you really are
taking impact on your on your fist and
your skin and this and that so you do
want to glove up on this but I wanted
this to be as closest to the original
Bob you know that's what I'm used to I
don't want the head to Flap around like
a fish and in this head it's it's just
to me it feels just like the same as the
original Bob
you know the head doesn't just wobble
back and forth the Torso is still strong
and yeah so as for the arms
it's not a big deal for me
um
I tried doing head kicks on the versus
Bob and you know
with with the height on this if you're
not flexible already then you really do
have to
but full force into your head kicks you
know and you know and I'm not I'm not
trying to do that with them versus Bob
you know I may go full power on heavy
bags but you know as for a dummy like
this I'm just using it for a technique
you know and a lot of my students I want
them to know what areas of the Torso
what areas of the lower body do you want
to attack properly technical you know
and the legs are great the legs are
filled with some type of foam it's a
hard foam and there are PVC pipes inside
which I'll show you later on in this
video
it zips up in the back for the Torso and
the zips on the middle here the middle
section which I'll show you here in a
bit but what's really cool is it does
allow you to put sandbags so it comes
with three sandbags and they're long and
they have velcro uh openings and you can
shut them by velcro you just pour 60
pounds of sand so it's 20 pounds in each
each area here in the Triangle
and it is not a lot of weight if you're
trying to go uh 100 on this so if you're
trying to attack by doing teeps you know
front kicks head kicks hooks
um you know it's it's gonna fly around I
keep this guy and he flew across the
room you know even with 60 pounds so a
lot of other individuals they use
dumbbells and they'll put the dumbbells
in the back uh over the over the sandbag
and that helps it does help quite a bit
you know and we're talking heavy
dumbbells like 35 pounds and up you know
you need two for the back and then that
way when you kick it you know he doesn't
fly
you know and fall over I want I want my
students to to know how to properly kick
on the inside
you know what I'm saying
I want them to know how to kick on the
front quads
on the outside of the quads
okay
this is huge
and also where to kick on the midsection
you know so it does give you
you know obstacles which are the arms
let's go ahead and take a look at the
back
okay so here's the back nice stitching
throughout the entire product here and
it's like a velcro top
and then a nice durable zipper and of
course you know
regular Bob back that we got here and it
does have paddings in here for the arms
but like I said you can remove the whole
jacket here and it just exposes the
regular Bob
so this can come down
so if you are
an individual that likes to train
head kicks
you know
um
and the arms are bothersome then you can
definitely remove this this is where
you'll find the zipper
it's got a nice zipper here
and so this lip here just goes all the
way around all the way around the dummy
go ahead and bring it down this way
now the dummy here has a plastic kind of
like a frisbee kind of fill here
it's a minute to go over
the Bob dummy on the inside of here is
just like your classic Bob dummy it does
have little notches inside so that way
you can put it on a post the original
post you know the ones you fill with
sand or water and that way you can raise
it up or down so that's cool
um but what it does
here is if you try to you know
deconstruct this entire thing
you know I'm not sure if the entire
jacket will come off but it does come
with foam
and then it exposes your
Bob dummy right here so it does look
like you can take off the entire jacket
off the Bob dummy
and like I said it does have foam here
I'll go ahead and
see if I can tilt it your way
if you can see that
so there is foam so there is foam here
it does have PVC pipe in here for some
type of foundation
and of course this foam here for the
midsection
so let's put your frisbee disc thing
there
it's your Bob
like that
all right so that's the versus Bob
and uh
you know for me again I would only
purchase this
mainly just so my students know where to
attack you know I can teach them power
form technique on the heavy bags and
also through sparring although if you're
trying to learn on your own you got to
know where you're trying to hit you know
the the your punches for the jaw solar
plex
you know core shots uh liver shot you
got you know fill impact of ribs and of
course the legs the legs are huge for
someone like me I would just stick to
heavy bag work
that's just me you know I practice a lot
on power
you know get your Technique down and
then do power but um yeah this is this
is great for students that you you need
to teach them that technical form or if
you're training at home and you have no
sparring partner you need some legs you
know you can kick a bag all day and
visualize yeah that would be where the
thigh is
you know or and as for inner kicks
you're just kicking on one side of the
back here you actually got that you know
for that inner kick
so
I like that that's cool so this is a
versus Bob there'll be a link down below
if you like to check it out your own and
purchase one yourself
I'd say it's a good investment for any
gym definitely I'd rather have a couple
of these guys in my gym than just
regular classic Bobs you know because I
can teach everybody technical
attacks to the legs so
all right so anyways thanks for watching
if you like what you saw like And
subscribe you know thank you for
everybody who has subscribed and viewing
my videos on this channel and uh as
always
couple cup